well this is Tomac from Palo Alto
这是Palo Alto的Tomac
education this is the machine learning
教育这是机器学习
for students series and today we're
对于学生系列，今天我们是
gonna be talking about stop forecasts
会谈论停止预测
we're going to begin today's lesson with
我们要开始今天的课程有
a question when did artificial
什么时候做人工的问题
intelligence practices start in finance
情报实践从金融开始
well to answer this question we have to
很好地回答这个问题 ，我们必须
take a step back before computers were
在电脑前退一步
used to do these types of trades one of
曾经做过这些类型的交易之一
the first uses of financial technology
金融科技的第一次使用
was for arbitrage and what that did was
是为了套利而做的是什么
that a lot of investment bankers to take
很多投资银行家都要采取
advantage of price mismatches at
价格不匹配的优势在于
different exchanges to make an unnatural
不同的交流使不自然
profit the graph you see behind me is
利润你在我身后看到的图表是
called a triangle trade and this is what
称三角贸易，这是什么
allowed traders to make that profit now
允许交易者现在赚取利润
that we have artificial intelligence you
我们有人工智能你
might be wondering hmm how is it
可能想知道嗯它是怎么回事
changing a finance industry well there's
很好地改变了金融业
three major ways that artificial
三种主要方法是人工
intelligence is changing the finance
情报正在改变金融
industry and this is through banking
行业，这是通过银行业
chatbox that's the first one algorithmic
聊天框是第一个算法
trading that's the second one and fraud
交易是第二个和欺诈
detection now banking chatbots
检测现在银行聊天机器人
are so powerful these days that they can
这些天他们可以如此强大
generate data about previous stock
生成有关以前库存的数据
prices as well as purchase stocks for
价格以及购买股票
you that's another way in which AI is
你是AI的另一种方式
making an impact in the financial sector
对金融业产生影响
and also through algorithmic trading
并通过算法交易
algorithms are so powerful today which
今天的算法是如此强大，其
we're able to predict future stock
我们能够预测未来的库存
prices with an accuracy over 50% fraud
价格超过50％的欺诈行为
detection in the transactions can also
在交易中检测也可以
be detected through artificial
通过人工检测
intelligence we're going to get into all
我们将全面了解情报
these a little later let's take a moment
稍后我们花一点时间
to talk about where finance and
谈地方金融和
artificial intelligence is today there's
今天有人工智能
almost zero technical limitations for
几乎没有技术限制
automated trading almost all trading
自动交易几乎所有交易
that's done on the stock exchange today
这对今天的证券交易所进行
is dumped by computers only in the bond
被计算机仅在债券中 倾销
market our treats still done by people
推销我们的款待仍由人做
and that's changing rapidly millions and
而这正在迅速改变数百万人
millions of dollars are spent today
今天花了 数百万美元
trying to get computerized advantages
试图获得计算机化的优势
against other competitors new companies
与其他竞争对手新公司对抗
are
是
to take business from payment processors
从支付处理商处获取业务
retail lending and many other fields
零售贷款和许多其他领域
that used to exclusively belong to large
以前只属于大型
banks in the past our official
银行过去我们的官方
intelligence is revolutionising the
情报正在彻底改变世界
financial space let's dive into
金融空间让我们深入了解
arbitrage just a little bit more so you
套利只是多一点，所以你
might be wondering what are its
可能想知道它是什么
applications
应用
well arbitrage itself is a very simple
套利本身很简单
concept it's when you buy something for
概念是当你买东西
a low price and oneexchange
低廉的价格和一次交换
and sell it for a higher price at
和出售以更高的 价格在
another exchange you can actually
你可以实际的另一个交流
perform arbitrage without really using
没有真正使用就执行套利
any data and a simple script could be
任何数据和简单的脚本都可以
developed to exploit price differences
开发利用价格差异
now this is where artificial
现在这是人为的
intelligence comes in someone with even
情报来自有人甚至
minimal coding experience could provide
最小的编码经验可以提供
something to detect and act on operative
检测并采取行动的东西
opportunities like this now regular
这样的机会现在经常发生
people can't profit normally because
人们不能正常获利，因为
professional traders to detect an act of
专业交易员检测行为
arbitrage opportunities more effectively
套利机会更有效
now artificial intelligence as it gets
如今，人工智能，因为它得到
better and stronger are likely going to
更好，更强很可能会
find arbitrage opportunities that
找到套利机会
investment bankers missed the reason why
投资银行家错过了原因
is because everything that goes into
是因为一切都进入了
arbitrage can be built into an equation
套利可以建立在一个方程式中
that artificial intelligence can act on
人工智能可以作用于
immediately what does the front lines
什么前线立即
and the artificial intelligence when the
当人工智能时
finance sector look like well it's high
金融业看起来很高
frequency trading versus high frequency
频率交易与高频率
training those people with scripts are
用脚本训练那些人
optimizing arbitrage and trying to
优化套利并尝试
exploit it faster than anyone else
比其他人更快地利用它
there are huge returns to the fastest
有最快的回报
person and anyone else who gets second
获得第二名的人和其他任何人
place is left behind firms hire
地方留下了公司雇用
mathematicians and computer programmers
数学家和计算机程序员
and engineers to make sure everything is
和工程师确保一切都是
running as fast as it can they even bid
尽可能快地跑，他们甚至出价
for connections that are physically
对于物理上的连接
closest to the exchange pricing on these
最接近这些交易所的价格
bids can go into the millions of dollars
出价可以达到数百万美元
and really what they're paying for is a
真的什么他们支付的是一个
connection that might be inches closer
可能距离更近的连接
than their competitors that's how
比他们的竞争对手更好
competitive this space really is and how
竞争这个空间真的是和如何
much they stand to gain for being that
很多他们进账的在于
much closer high frequency trading
更接近高频交易
persist
坚持
frequency trading is really the front
频率交易真的是前沿
line and getting the most money out of
线并获得最 赚钱出
the financial sector using artificial
金融业使用人工
intelligence generally speaking for most
一般来说，智力最多
normal people the advice artificial
正常人的建议是人为的
intelligence can give you is just as
情报可以给你就是这样
good or better than someone with an MBA
比拥有MBA学位的人好或好
degree or degree in finance it's
在金融学士学位或学位是
actually cheaper too this is huge for
实际上更便宜，这是巨大的
financial technology researchers are
金融技术研究人员
trying to create the best investing
试图创造最好的投资
robot for someone to invest their money
机器人为某人投资他们的钱
through and it's already been proven
通过，它已经被证实
that artificial intelligence
人工智能
consistently outperforms human investors
始终优于人类投资者
traders don't like to admit it but
交易者不喜欢承认这一点，但
they've been beaten for years just like
他们已经打了多年，就像
our friend here he's gotten a little
我们的朋友在这里他得到了一点点
frustrated that the computer can give
计算机可以给予沮丧
actual advice and give it better up to
实际的建议，并让它更好
this point we've shown that artificial
这一点我们已经证明了人为的
intelligence is really making strides in
情报正在大踏步前进
financial technology it's taking the
它采取的金融技术
lead and it's replacing jobs and
领导和它正在取代工作和
outperforming human behavior so the
超越人类行为所以
natural question is can artificial
自然的问题是可以人为的
intelligence algorithm fail well the
智能算法失败了
answer is yes and it has before in the
答案是肯定的，而且之前的答案是肯定的
past now the reason why these algorithms
过去现在这些算法的原因
fail is because they are programmed by
失败是因为他们被编程了
people using mathematics and they sent
人们使用数学和他们发送
different thresholds for different
针对不同的不同的阈值
behaviors as a matter of fact the stock
行为事实上是股票
market lost trillions of dollars for 38
市场损失了数万亿美元的38美元
minutes one day in 2010 because of
2010年的一天分钟因为
trading like this all the algorithms
像这样交易所有的算法
were set to a similar threshold and when
被设置为类似的阈值，何时
stocks reached that threshold they
股票达到了他们的门槛
immediately sold off all their holdings
立刻卖掉了他们所有的股份
creating this flash crash we're gonna
创造这个闪光崩溃，我们将要
start getting into some technical
开始进入一些技术
details about how these algorithms work
这些算法如何工作的详细信息
in order to do that we need to take a
为了做到这一点，我们需要采取
step back and talk about what the
退一步说说什么
difference is between classification and
差异在于分类和
regression the main difference between
回归主要区别
the two of them is the type of output
他们 两个的是 输出 的类型
that they give you for classification
他们给你分类
problems and algorithm is designed to
问题和算法旨在
give you an output that tells you a
给你一个 告诉你 的输出
specific thing whether or not say for
具体的事情是否说
example something is a dog a fish or a
例如某种东西是狗或鱼
cat with regression problems the output
猫有回归问题的输出
that the algorithm tries to give you is
该算法试图给你的是
the value of some number now when we're
我们现在的某个数字的价值
talking about financial
谈到金融
the algorithms typically what we want to
算法通常是我们想要的
find out are things like stock prices
找出像股票价格这样的东西
we're going to get into regression a
我们要进入回归a
little more detail now what is linear
更多细节现在什么是线性的
regression well it's actually fairly
很好地回归它实际上是公平的
simple linear regression tries to find
简单的线性回归试图找到
the best straight line through data
通过数据的最佳直线
points that's it
这就是它
and you can see behind me there's a red
你可以看到我身后有一个红色
line through all the data points that is
通过所有数据点
actually the line that has the least
实际上是最少的线
amount of distance between all of those
所有这些之间的距离
points and the line we use a model like
点，线，我们使用像模特
this to help predict the outcome of
这有助于预测结果
different trends in our case for any
在我们的案例中任何不同的趋势
additional day on the stock exchange we
我们在证券交易所上市的另一天
can check what the next day is going to
可以检查第二天会发生什么
be given its past performance what are
得到它过去的表现是什么
some other types of regression well of
一些其他类型的回归井
course there's nonlinear ways that you
当然，你有非线性方式
can do regression on data one of those
可以在这些数据的一个做回归
ways is through a neural network now
方法是通过神经网络现在
these use nodes connections and weights
这些使用节点连接和权重
between the output of a predictive
在预测的输出之间
number I made a simple truck for you
我为你做了一辆简单的卡车
behind me but the truth is is that a
在我身后，但事实是是，
neural network is more like a black box
神经网络更像是一个黑盒子
where we can't really figure out how the
在哪里我们无法弄清楚如何
mechanics inside really work we give it
里面的力学我们给它真正的工作
information and then it provides us with
然后将它提供给 我们的信息
an answer
一个答案
another type of nonlinear regression is
另一种类型的非线性回归是
a decision tree and a decision tree is a
决策树和决策树是
computerized flowchart it just uses a
计算机化的流程图它只使用了一个
series of if-then statements and
一系列if-then 语句和
provides you with the graph of what your
为您提供您的图表
expected Palpa would be another type of
预计帕尔帕将是另一种类型
regressor would be the K nearest
回归量将是最近的K.
neighbors or kN and model now this finds
邻居或kN和模型现在发现
data that is similar to unknown data
与未知数据类似的数据
points and then averages the value of
点然后平均值
the outcomes to give your prediction
给出预测的结果
think about it like this if you're a
如果你是一个人，请考虑这样
student and you studied for three hours
学生和你学习了三个小时
and got a B+ on a test and another
并且在测试和另一个测试中获得了B +
student also studied for three hours
学生也学了三个小时
you'd expect that other student to also
你也希望其他学生也能参加
get a B+ for those of you who are
为那些你的人获得B +
curious about neural networks I wanted
对我想要的神经网络感到好奇
to go into them in a little bit more
进入他们更多一点
detail now neural networks are extremely
细节现在神经网络非常
complicated and don't have good
复杂而且没有好处
interpretations remember we just said
解释记得我们刚刚说过
that
那
kind of like a back box now they take
现在他们就像一个后箱
inputs the data that we know and send
输入我们知道并发送的数据
them through a bunch of notes or neurons
他们通过一堆笔记或神经元
then they give us an output these
然后他们给我们输出这些
outputs are created using an
输出是使用a创建的
evolutionary procedure so we start with
进化程序，所以我们开始
random waits for the connections between
随机等待之间的联系
the notes and slowly randomly sometimes
笔记， 有时慢慢随机
these weights are changed to find the
这些权重被改变以找到
combination of weights that gives us the
赋予我们权重的组合
network that most closely predicts the
最密切预测的网络
data that we trained on if this is
我们接受过培训的数据
confusing to you don't worry that's okay
对你感到困惑并不担心这没关系
I just wanted to give you a little bit
我只是想给你一点点
more information on neural network since
有关神经网络的更多信息
it's such a hot topic in machine
它是机器中如此热门的话题
learning and artificial intelligence
学习和人工智能
right now we're going to get a little
现在我们会得到一点点
bit into the finance world here we're
我们在这里进入金融世界
gonna ask ourselves a question what are
要问自己一个问题是什么
the impacts of active and passive
主动和被动的影响
investing well artificial intelligence
投资良好的人工智能
and financial technology has to move
和金融技术必须移动
much of the heavy lifting to automated
大部分繁重的自动化
investment models there's firms like
投资模式有公司喜欢
betterment and wealthfront that have
改善和wealthfront有
made investing about as passive as it
投资就像它一样被动
could possibly get they both have
可能会得到他们两个
automatic deposits into investment
自动存入投资
accounts and can run without any
帐户，可以没有任何运行
supervision down this type of investment
监督此类投资
using index funds and simple risk-based
使用指数基金和简单的基于风险的
allocations have pushed out a lot of the
分配推出了很多
active investing think about it machines
积极投资考虑机器
have taken over a lot of the rules
已经接管了很多规则
already and now we've gone from active
已经和现在我们已经离开了
investing where human beings were making
投资于人类所在的地方
direct calls on stock prices to or
直接调用股票价格或
passive investing where machines are
机器所在的被动投资
making calls based on rules based
基于规则进行呼叫
algorithms now the amount of money
算法现在的金额
invested in index funds right now which
现在投资于指数基金 ，其
track our stock market as a whole
跟踪我们的股票市场整体
rather than investing in a single stock
而不是投资单一股票
has soared people not believe that you
飙升的人不相信你
shouldn't bother trying to beat the
不应该打扰试图击败
market now there are some strength
市场现在有一些实力
towards active investing and the
积极投资和
strengths of active investing is that
积极投资的优势在于
it's flexible delivers higher returns
它灵活， 提供更高的回报
and allows you to hedge now passive
并允许你对冲现在被动
investing offers low fees last decision
投资提供低费用的最后决定
making and is tax efficient so there's
制作并且税收效率如​​此之高
two sides to this active investment
这项积极投资的双方
weakness is higher fees and higher taxes
弱点是更高的费用和更高的税收
and it's very susceptible to long term
而且它很容易受到长期影响
volatility
挥发性
on the other hand weaknesses of passive
另一方面被动的弱点
investing his long-term investments are
投资他的长期投资是
unable to perform the market and then it
无法进入市场然后它
is rigid so now that you have a better
是僵硬的， 所以现在你有一个更好的
understanding of the some of the
的一些理解
financial backgrounds between active and
活跃与积极的金融背景
passive investing we're going to start
我们将开始被动投资
moving on to some other topics for you
继续 为您介绍其他一些主题
to explore in this lesson we're going to
我们将在本课中探索
go over a time series forecasting
查看时间序列预测
analysis using Apple's stock price
使用Apple的股票价格进行分析
before we get into that example I want
在我们进入我想要的那个例子 之前
to take a moment to show you what the
花点时间向你展示一下
data looks like the chart behind me
数据看起来就像我背后的图表
shows four things of the stock it shows
显示它显示的股票的四件事
the opening price the high price of the
开盘价高价格
day and the closing price along with the
一天和收盘价一起
volume using this information we're
我们使用这些信息
going to try and predict what the future
要尝试预测 未来 是什么
price of the stock is going to be I hope
股票价格将是我希望
you're excited to go through this
你很高兴能够完成这件事
example because I'm excited to show it
例如，因为我很高兴能够展示它
to you I just showed you the data that
对你我只是向你展示了那些数据
we're going to be using in the example
我们将 要使用的例子
for this lesson I wanted to give you an
对于本课，我想给你一个
opportunity to take a look at what it
机会来 看看它是什么
actually looks like now you can see the
实际上看起来你现在可以看到了
data behind me here and a
我身后的数据和一个
comma-separated file it gives us the
它给我们的逗号分隔文件
dates the opening price closing price
以开盘价收盘价为准
and volume for the stocks that are
和股票的数量
traded for Apple I want to go over the
交易苹果我想过去
code flow chart that we're going to be
我们将要成为的代码流程图
using as a step by step approach to show
使用如一步步的方法来显示
you how to create your own model using
你如何使用创建自己的模型
financial data I'm going to take a step
财务数据我要迈出一步
out of the screen and we're going to go
离开屏幕，我们要走了
over each step in our demonstration
在我们演示的每一步
today so let's take a look at this code
今天让我们来看看这段代码吧
flow chart the first step will be to
流程图的第一步骤将是
import a bunch of Python packages the
进口一堆Python包的
next thing that we're going to do is
接下来我们要做的就是
load the data now you know what that
加载数据现在你知道那是什么
data looks like we've shown you the
数据看起来像我们已经向您展示了
charts and we've also physically shown
图表，我们也身体显示
you the data in order to run the model
您是数据以运行模型
you'll need to load it in and that's the
你需要加载它，那就是
second step the third step is going to
第三步骤是 要第二步骤
be defining the model and then the
定义模型，然后是
fourth step is going to be plotting a
第四步是策划一个
graph of the output of the model I'm
我是模型输出的图表
going to go over each one of these four
要经历这四个中的每一个
steps for you in detail and show you the
为您详细介绍并向您展示的步骤
code that's used to create the algorithm
用于创建算法的 代码
are you ready let's go don't worry
你准备好让我们 不用担心
everyone
大家
I'm still here what we're gonna be doing
我还在这里，我们将要做的事情
now is go over the actual code used in
现在回顾一下实际使用的代码
the algorithm and remember we're trying
该算法并记住我们正在努力
to predict the price of Apple's stock
预测苹果股票的价格
and I've already shown you the chart
而且我已经向你展示了图表
that shows that stock prices the high
这表明股价高涨
the low the close and the volume we've
我们的收盘价和收盘价都很低
taken a look at what the data actually
看看实际数据是什么
looks like in a comma separated file and
看起来像一个逗号分隔的文件和
we've gone over the code flow chart so
我们已经查看了代码流程图
that you know the different steps in the
你知道在不同的步骤
algorithm we're going to start with our
算法我们将从我们的开始
first step and that's importing our
第一步，那是导入我们的
Python packages as you can see here
你可以在这里看到 Python包
we're using several different packages
我们正在使用几种不同的包
including our CSV package to loading the
包括我们的CSV包加载
data our numpy and sidekick passages
数据我们的numpy和sidekick段落
packages to do the data processing and
包进行数据处理和
our matplotlib package in order to graph
我们的matplotlib包以便图表
our results step two is where we load
我们的研究结果第二步是我们加载
the data now we create two lists right
数据现在我们创建了两个正确的列表
up front seats and prices and those
前排座位和价格以及那些
empty lists are going to be filled with
空列表将要充满
data from our CSV file now the next
我们的CSV文件中的数据现在是下一个
thing that we do is define a function to
我们做的事情就是定义一个函数来
go ahead and open up the file and get
继续打开文件然后获取
the data out of it and then we go ahead
数据出来， 然后我们继续前进
and get our data using that function
并使用该函数获取我们的数据
from our Apple dot CSV file alright
从我们的Apple dot CSV文件好吧
everyone let's get into the next couple
每个人都让我们进入下一对夫妇
of steps of our algorithm step number
我们的算法步的步数
three is where we define the model now
三是我们 现在定义模型的地方
we go ahead and define a predict price
我们继续并定义预测价格
function that's going to go ahead and
这个功能将继续发展
give us the future prices of our stock
给我们未来的股票价格
given the historical prices and the data
鉴于历史价格和数据
that we feed it the fourth step in the
我们喂它的第四步
algorithm is where we go ahead and
算法是我们继续前进，
create our plot graph that plots our
创建我们绘制的情节图
output in the fifth and final step is
第五步也是最后一步的输出是
where we use that defined model to
我们在哪里使用定义的模型
predict the prices our stock for the
预测我们股票的价格
next 29 days and that's it wasn't it
接下来的29天，那就不是了
easy in just a few lines of code we were
容易在短短的几行代码我们
able to take a dataset with historical
能够采用历史数据集
stock prices and predict future stock
股票价格和预测未来股票
prices how cool is that you can go ahead
价格是多么酷，你可以继续前进
and repeat the example that we just went
并重复我们刚才去 的例子
over on new data so a different stock if
如果是新的数据那么不同的股票
you want or on new models now here's a
你想要或现在的新型号这里是一个
project
项目
can work on try to make your own model
可以尝试制作自己的模型
maybe add some extra data you can
也许可以添加一些额外的数据
predict Apple stock based on iPhone
预测基于iPhone的Apple股票
sales or Amazon stock based on sales of
基于销售额的销售额或亚马逊股票
the echo the model that we went over was
回声我们过去的模型是
actually pretty simple and was just
实际上很简单而且只是
based on time series data we can do even
基于时间序列数据，我们甚至可以做到
better and become even more accurate
更好，变得更加准确
with different data I challenge you to
我挑战你的不同数据
explore this further another exercise I
再探讨这个另一个练习我
have for you has to deal with weather
有你必须应对天气
now this is a little bit harder of a
现在这有点难了
question and it's meant to inspire you
问题，这是为了激励你
make you think make you want to
让你想到你想要的
experiment now it's a little similar to
实验现在它有点类似于
predicting stock in that they're very
预测股票是非常的
different but both have elements of
不同， 但两者都有
randomness and elements and allow them
随机性和元素并允许它们
to be predicted think about it we could
有待预测，我们可以考虑一下
use things like yesterday's weather
使用昨天的天气
climate data or the weather in the next
气候数据或下一天的天气
city over to predict our own weather try
城市过来预测我们自己的天气尝试
to think about how predicting weather
思考如何预测天气
it's different from predicting stock
它与预测股票不同
prices but how we could use that towards
价格，但我们如何使用 朝向
our advantage in creating a model if
我们在创造 ，如果模式的优势
you're curious about the chatbox
你对聊天盒很好奇
we've mentioned earlier in this lesson
我们 在本课程前面已经提到了
take a look at the YouTube video behind
看看背后的YouTube视频
me on how kindnesses chatbox are making
我对聊天盒的好意做出了什么
finance simpler
财务更简单
I'm sure you'll really enjoy learning
我相信你真的很喜欢学习
about their chatbox and how it's making
关于他们的聊天室以及它是如何制作的
finance even better if you want to get
如果你想获得，财务会更好
an even deeper understanding of
更深刻的理解
artificial intelligence and finance take
人工智能与金融
a look at this webinar on the
看看这个网络研讨会
applications of machine learning in the
机器学习在中国的应用
financial sector you'll really get an
金融部门， 你真的会得到一个
in-depth look at how artificial
深入了解如何人工
intelligence and machine learning is
智能和机器学习是
being used in finance I hope all of you
在金融中使用我希望你们所有人
have gotten really excited about
真的很兴奋
artificial intelligence in the financial
人工智能在金融
industry if you're curious and want to
如果你很好奇并希望这个行业
learn more we've got some excellent
了解更多我们有一些优秀
books here that you can pick up and read
这里的书籍，你可以拿起和阅读
we have flash boys by Michael Lewis
我们有迈克尔刘易斯的闪光男孩
advanced analytics and artificial
高级分析和人工
intelligence by Tony bubier
智能托尼 bubier
advances in financial machines by Marcos
Marcos在金融机器方面的进步
Lopez de Prairie Lewis now if you decide
Lopez de Prairie Lewis，如果你决定的话
to read flash boys by Michael Lewis I've
迈克尔刘易斯读 我的闪光男孩
got a great question for you to think
你有一个很好的问题要想
about as you go through the book what
关于你经历这本书的内容
happens when you take algorithms too far
当你把算法放得太远时会发生
Michael Lewis
about traders unfairly gaming the market
关于交易者不公平地游戏市场
using their algorithms think about that
使用他们的算法考虑这一点
flash crash we talked about earlier the
我们之前谈过的闪电崩溃了
lessons and the implications that it has
经验教训和它 具有的影响
on the stock market as a whole
在股市整体上
this is Tomac from palo alto education i
这是来自palo alto education的Tomaci
want to thank you again for learning
我想再次感谢你的学习
with me today
今天和我在一起